

# **Mochamad Rizky Purnama**

Jl. Mengger Girang no.60 Regol Kota Bandung 40254 +6289621372302, mochamadrizkypurnama@gmail.com

### PERSONAL PROFILE

I have worked in information technology industry with 8+ years of experience and been involved in various projects specifically in the areas of Front-End for web-oriented application. I have strong will for learning and can work as personal or team.

### **EDUCATION**

# Islamic State University Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung

2014-2021

Bandung, Indonesia Informatics Engineering

**SMKN 4 Bandung** 

2011-2014

Bandung, Indonesia Computer & Network Engineering

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Front-End Developer at Eresto Digital Indonesia,** Bandung November 2020 – Present *A startup company that provides consulting services and application for improve and organize their business. The main product of Eresto Digital Indonesia is an ERP and POS System, also management reseller call "SQUIDS".* 

### **Project Experience**

- Develop and Maintenance Application Eresto (November 2020 Present) As Front end Developer (Technologies used : HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular JS, Semantic UI, Ionic, Cordova)
  - Maintenance and Develop Backoffice such Inventory Management, Purchasing Module, CRM, HRM, Sales Reports and Accounting Module
  - Maintenance and Develop POS system
  - Maintenance and Develop Kitchen Display from POS system
- Develop and Maintenance SQUIDS (May 2021 Present) As Front end Developer (Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React JS, Material UI)
  - Maintenance and Develop Reseller Web
  - Maintenance and Develop Storefront Web
  - Maintenance and Develop Admin Web
  - Maintenance and Develop User Web

Front-End Developer at Techno Line Indonesia, Bandung January 2012 – January 2020 A startup company that provides consulting services in all areas of information technology issues such as consulting, information system design, application development, and planning design. The main product of Technoline Indonesia is an ERP System called TerraNova System. The customer of Technoline Indonesia spreads across Indonesia which are PT. Indricipta Aditama, Persatuan Olahraga Selam Seluruh Indonesia (POSSI), PT. ALMEGA JAYA, D'riam River Side Resort, PT. Hasta Luhur Abadi, Kota Baru Parahyangan, Universitas Islam Nusantara, etc.

As Web Developer & Front End Developer, Responsible for system development and manufacturing of web-based applications.

## **Project Experience**

- Developed ERP System for Retail Company, PT. Indricipta Aditama (June 2017-January 2020) As Front end Developer (Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Laravel, Javascript, Bootstrap)
  - Making Company Profile for Retail Company Grutty
  - Making HR Module with team
  - Making Interface POS(Point Of Sale)
  - Making all printable report
  - Provide training and educating the use of POS application for user POS
- Developed the information system and e-commerce for Persatuan Olahraga Selam Seluruh Indonesia (POSSI) (February 2017-January 2019) As Front End Developer (Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Laravel, Javascript, Bootstrap)
  - Making Company Profile of POSSI
  - Making Core Desain for Admin POSSI
  - Making all printable report
  - Making card POSSI
- Developed the mini ERP System for Flour distributor PT. Hasta Luhur Abadi as Front End Developer
- Developed the information system for Universitas Islam Nusantara (August 2013- August 2014) As Web Designer
- Developed the Mobile Learning website for Universitas Islam Nusantara. (January 2012-March 2013) As Web Designer

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Familiar with these technologies:
  - Operating System: Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8.1, Windows 10, Debian Linux, Linux Mint, Ubuntu Linux, Mac OS
  - Databases: MySQL
  - Application Development and Programming Technologies: Java, PHP, HTML, CSS, CI, Laravel, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, SQL, GIT, Text Editor, Angular JS, React IS
  - Office Suite: Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point
- Participant in 'Digital Talent Scholarsip Junior Mobile Programming' (July 2019); an event that was held by Kementerian Komunikasi dan Informatika RI.